Let us pray eternal Lord God who by the Holy Spirit presided at the Council of the Apostles
to guide them in all knowledge and truth be present with those who take council in this
place and those who govern in Miami. In the passions of debate give them a quiet
spirit and the complexities of the issues give them clear minds and in the
moments of decision give them courageous hearts. Guide them in all things to seek
only your glory and the good of your world. Through our Lord. Amen.
To the Republic for which it stands, one nation, a new God, indivisible with liberty and justice for all.
I would forward the public opinion and special personal appearance of the audience
who wishes to address the council on the agenda.
There are being nine. Item five, the consent agenda.
Staff is recommending items six through ten for the consent agenda.
There are no questions or objections with any motion.
And second. Second. Roll call please.
Jonathan. Aye.
Court is adjourned. Aye.
Wetson. Aye. Lewis. Aye. Schultz. Aye.
Item 11 is new business and a new business. Steen or anyone? Nothing to be
your honor. Item 12 is staff reports.
It's important to pack it. The staff is available for any questions.
If there are none, we'll move to item 13, trustee community announcements.
Any announcements?
Item 14 is adjourned. Do we have a motion to adjourn?
Motion adjourned. And second. Second.
Roll call please.
Weston. Aye. Lewis. Aye.
Forester. Aye. Johnson. Aye. Schultz. Aye.
Thank you. We're going to.